let quiz = [
    {
        question: " Which of the following is the correct way of declaring an array?",
        option: [
            "array javatpoint[10]; ",
            "int javatpoint[10];",
            "int javatpoint;",
            "int javatpoint[10];",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following highly uses the concept of an array?",
        option: [
            "Binary search tree",
            "Caching",
            "Scheduling a process",
            "Spatial locality",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is the size of int arr[9] assuming that int is of 4 bytes?",
        option: [
            "9",
            "35",
            "36",
            "none above these",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is the process of inserting an element in the stack?",
        option: [
            "Push",
            "Add",
            "Insert",
            "None of Above",
        ],
        answer: 1,   
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:",
        option: [
            "Linked list",
            "Stack",
            "Binary tree",
            "Queue",
        ],
        answer: 2,   
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following principle does Queue use?",
        option: [
            "FIFO principle",
            "Linear tree",
            "Ordered array",
            "LIFO principle",
        ],
        answer: 1,   
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the infix expression?",
        option: [
            "A-B+C",
            "ABC+*",
            "+A*BC",
            "A+B*C",
        ],
        answer: 4,   
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these elements are all <table> elements?",
        option: [
            "<table> <tr> <td>",
            "<table> <tr> <tt>",
            "<table> <body> <tr>",
            "<table> <head> <tfoot>",
        ],
        answer: 1,   
    },
    {
        question: "The minimum number of stacks required to implement a stack is __",
        option: [
            "3",
            "1",
            "2",
            "10",
        ],
        answer: 3,   
    },
    {
        question: "What is another name for the circular queue among the following options?",
        option: [
            "Rectangle buffer",
            "Square buffer",
            "None of the above",
            "Ring buffer",
        ],
        answer: 4,   
    },
]